var game = {
    questions : [
        {
            question : "How did Odin lose his eye",
            answers : ["In the battle with Jodenheim", "Pulled out by an eagle while on a quest", "To win all battles until the end of time", "To drink from the pool of the Norns"],
            answer : "To drink from the pool of the Norns",
        },
        {
            question : "What are the names of Loki's offspring",
            answers : ["Hella and Fenrir", "Frigg and Frigga", "Hella and Freyja", "Hoognir and Munjir"],
            answer : "Hella and Fenrir",
        },
        {
            question : "Which god or godess lost their hand to a giant wolf",
            answers : ["Balder", "Tyr", "Heimdal", "Rigg"],
            answer : "Tyr",
        },
        {
            question : "What is one of Heimdal's disguised names",
            answers : ["Munin", "Sigfruin", "Rigg", "Bouldin"],
            answer : "Rigg",
        },
        {
            question : "Which one of the following is NOT one of the nine realms",
            answers : ["Hafleheim", "Nifleheim", "Helheim", "Vaniheim"],
            answer : "Hafleheim",
        },
        {
            question : "How many children did Thor have",
            answers : ["None", "1", "2", "3"],
            answer : "3",
        },
        {
            question : "Who gave birth to Odin's horse, Sleipnir",
            answers : ["the horse that pulls the world around the sun", "the frost giant's King's horse", "Loki", "Fenris"],
            answer : "3",
        },
        {
            question : "Who wept tears of gold when they thought they were going to have to marry and ugly stone smith",
            answers : ["Frigga", "Freyja", "Indunna", "Sif"],
            answer : "Freyja",
        },
        {
            question : "What food kept the gods youthful",
            answers : ["Mead", "Honey", "Nectar", "Apples"],
            answer : "Apples",
        },
        {
            question : "What creature does Thor kill, but in turn dies from his wounds in Ragnarok",
            answers : ["Jormongand", "Fenrir", "Loki", "Surter"],
            answer : "Apples",
        },
        {
            question : "What is the name of Odin's spear",
            answers : ["Mjolnir", "Gungnir", "Yggridsil", "Hagrath"],
            answer : "Gungnir",
        },
        {
            question : "Who kills the god Kvasir",
            answers : ["Jormongand", "Fenrir", "dwarves", "dark elves"],
            answer : "dwarves",
        },
    ]
}